





Important

Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

Summary

Jump to Section

Verified : Email - id

Last Active: Jan-Mar 2021

Result-oriented Professional with 20 years of experience in Solution Design, Business Analysis, Business Consulting, Service Delivery, Process Enhancement, Project Management, Risk Management, Technical Specifications, Impact Analysis, Business Process Mapping, Presales

Work Experience

Ericsson as Senior Solution Architect Jan 2016 to Till Date

Analysis, Business Process Mapping, Presales

Last Modified: Jan-Mar 2021

Work Experience | Education |

- Tech Mahindra as Principal Solution Architect Sep 2014 to Jul 2016
- Ericsson as Enterprise Solution Architect Jul 2011 to Aug 2014

Perceiving & delivering end-to-end requirement and solution design for Clients across the globe Ensuring delivery of projects from conceptualization to delivery within preset budgets and deadlines Understanding & adopting emerging trends & techniques, addressing the industry requirements to achieve organizational objectives

Monitoring the business process mapping, requirement study, defining the various specifications for application implementation, and client interaction for resolving concerns

Building & maintaining relations with clients, generating business from the existing accounts and achieving profitability and sales growth

Providing demos of the proposals to clients, providing solution strategy (pre-sales) support encompassing briefing on client feedback / insights to help them in developing customer-specific strategies Leading, training & monitoring the performance of team members to ensure efficiency in sales and meeting of

individual & group targets

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.A (Economics) from Delhi University in 1997

PG: PG Diploma (Computer Application) from MADURAI KAMARAJ UNIVERSITY in 2001

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:
Dockers & Kubernetes basic training

SHL - L1 Leadership Assessment
TMFORUM Certified (L2) Enterprise Architect
Ericsson CBiO (ETCP) Certified (Professional)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Bengali				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.